<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips on .Net Programmer Incubator</title>
    <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tags/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips on .Net Programmer Incubator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s style up our appliction with Bootswatch!</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/bootswatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/bootswatch/</guid>
      <description>Bootswatch is a free collection of Bootstrap themes that offers a variety of easy-to-use and customizable themes for quickly adding visual style to Bootstrap websites or applications.
Each theme comes with a CSS file and optional JavaScript files for convenience and customization.
Bootswatch is a great way to add style and visual appeal to Bootstrap projects without spending a lot of time designing and coding from scratch.
Now that we have our application up and running, let&amp;rsquo;s style it up with Bootswatch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Database</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/change_database/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/change_database/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have a custom registration form, we need to change the database if we want to save the data in a specific database. In this article, we will change the database created in one article to another database of ours.
Let&amp;rsquo;s check the existing database in SQL Server Object Explorer: Go to &amp;ldquo;View&amp;rdquo; menu at the top of the screen, and click &amp;ldquo;SQL Server Object Explorer&amp;rdquo; from the dropdown menu to open SQL Server Object Explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/github_copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/github_copilot/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Copilot is an artificial intelligence (AI) powered code assistant that is built on OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT (Generative Pre-trained Transformer) model. It is designed to help developers write code more efficiently by generating code suggestions based on the context of what the developer is working on. GitHub Copilot is currently available as a preview for Visual Studio Code, and it is free to use. GitHub Copilot can be used as a plugin for Visual Studio Code, and it works by analyzing the code in real-time, along with the comments and the context of the code, and suggests code snippets and functions that are relevant to the developer&amp;rsquo;s task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET MVC?</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/asp.net_mvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/asp.net_mvc/</guid>
      <description>ASP.NET Core is a web framework that can be used to build web applications and services. It provides a lot of features such as cross-platform support, high-performance, middleware, dependency injection, configuration, routing, and logging.
On the other hand, ASP.NET Core MVC is an extension of ASP.NET Core that specifically focuses on building web applications using the Model-View-Controller (MVC) pattern. The MVC pattern is a design pattern that separates the application logic into three interconnected components: the Model (data layer), View (user interface), and Controller (application logic).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
