<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>.Net Programmer Incubator</title>
    <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on .Net Programmer Incubator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Blog</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/about_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/about_blog/</guid>
      <description>By writing a blog, I can better understand the technologies and application methods of .NET and share them with you. This is a great plan! Here are some steps you can follow to start your journey in learning .NET and building web apps with ASP.NET Core:
1. Install Visual Studio:
Visual Studio is an integrated development environment (IDE) used for .NET development. You can download the latest version of Visual Studio from the official Microsoft website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Appliction in Asp.Net Core MVC</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Create our first project in Asp.Net Core MVC: Open Visual Studio and click on &amp;ldquo;Create a new project&amp;rdquo; from the start menu. Select the ASP.NET Core Web App (Model-View-Controller) template and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;. Enter a name for your project and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;. Select the &amp;ldquo;.NET 7.0(Standard Term Support)&amp;rdquo; or latest version framework and clic &amp;ldquo;Create&amp;rdquo;. The project is created and the &amp;ldquo;Solution Explorer&amp;rdquo; window is displayed. close the &amp;ldquo;Welcome&amp;rdquo; window and click on Index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/getting_started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/getting_started/</guid>
      <description>Install Visual Studio: Go to the Visual Studio download page on the Microsoft website. The link is https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/.
1. The choice of which edition to use depends on your needs and budget. If you&amp;rsquo;re an individual developer or a student, the Community edition is likely sufficient.
If you&amp;rsquo;re working on a small team and need more advanced features, the Professional edition may be a better fit.
And if you&amp;rsquo;re part of a large organization that needs the most advanced tools and features, the Enterprise edition is the way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register and Login</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/register_and_login/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/register_and_login/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Create a database first register form: Right-click on &amp;ldquo;Models&amp;rdquo; and move the mouse to the &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo; button, then a new window with many options appears, click &amp;ldquo;class&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;. Enter a name for your new class and click &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo;. Edit new properties in the class file. Open the file &amp;ldquo;ApplicationDbContext.cs&amp;rdquo; in the &amp;ldquo;Data&amp;rdquo; folder and add Dbset the new class will just be created. Right-click on any of the folders in &amp;ldquo;Solution Explorer&amp;rdquo; and move the mouse to the &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo; button, then a new window with many options appears, click &amp;ldquo;New Scaffolded Item&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET MVC?</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tips/asp.net_mvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tips/asp.net_mvc/</guid>
      <description>ASP.NET Core is a web framework that can be used to build web applications and services. It provides a lot of features such as cross-platform support, high-performance, middleware, dependency injection, configuration, routing, and logging.
On the other hand, ASP.NET Core MVC is an extension of ASP.NET Core that specifically focuses on building web applications using the Model-View-Controller (MVC) pattern. The MVC pattern is a design pattern that separates the application logic into three interconnected components: the Model (data layer), View (user interface), and Controller (application logic).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
