<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASP.NET CORE MVC on .Net Programmer Incubator</title>
    <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tags/asp.net-core-mvc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ASP.NET CORE MVC on .Net Programmer Incubator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/tags/asp.net-core-mvc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Admin &amp; User Role</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/admin_and_user/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/admin_and_user/</guid>
      <description>What are the Admin and User roles in ASP.NET used for? The Admin and User roles are used to control access to different areas of a web application based on the user&amp;rsquo;s role.
The Admin role typically has access to all areas of the application, including sensitive administrative functions such as user management, system settings, and other restricted areas.
The User role, on the other hand, typically has limited access to the application and can only perform certain actions or access certain areas of the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register form</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/register/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will create a custom registration form and add it to the application.
Let&amp;rsquo;s Create a database first register form: Right-click on &amp;ldquo;Models&amp;rdquo; and move the mouse to the &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo; button, then a new window with many options appears, click &amp;ldquo;class&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;. Enter a name for your new class and click &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo;. Edit new properties in the class file. Open the file &amp;ldquo;ApplicationDbContext.cs&amp;rdquo; in the &amp;ldquo;Data&amp;rdquo; folder and add Dbset the new class will just be created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET MVC?</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/asp.net_mvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/asp.net_mvc/</guid>
      <description>ASP.NET Core is a web framework that can be used to build web applications and services. It provides a lot of features such as cross-platform support, high-performance, middleware, dependency injection, configuration, routing, and logging.
On the other hand, ASP.NET Core MVC is an extension of ASP.NET Core that specifically focuses on building web applications using the Model-View-Controller (MVC) pattern. The MVC pattern is a design pattern that separates the application logic into three interconnected components: the Model (data layer), View (user interface), and Controller (application logic).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lien-chu.github.io/IncubatorBlog.io/post/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will create our first application in Asp.Net Core MVC.
Let&amp;rsquo;s Create our first project in Asp.Net Core MVC: Open Visual Studio and click on &amp;ldquo;Create a new project&amp;rdquo; from the start menu. Select the ASP.NET Core Web App (Model-View-Controller) template and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;. Enter a name for your project and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;. Select the &amp;ldquo;.NET 7.0(Standard Term Support)&amp;rdquo; or latest version framework and clic &amp;ldquo;Create&amp;rdquo;. The project is created and the &amp;ldquo;Solution Explorer&amp;rdquo; window is displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
